<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Vitor Caneppele</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Vitor Caneppele</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 12:51:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Should Not Be Our God</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/knowledgeisnotmygod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 12:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/knowledgeisnotmygod/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s world, we often find ourselves in relentless pursuit of knowledge, productivity, and self-improvement—especially at a young age when we are just starting our professional journeys. We chase validation, admire brilliant individuals, and strive to prove our worth. This pursuit is undoubtedly a beautiful thing, and there is value in it. However, it is important to recognize that we must continuously evolve and adapt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through this ongoing process of growth and change, it becomes evident that knowledge and self-improvement should not be seen as ultimate goals or idols. They will never provide complete satisfaction. The drive to tackle difficult challenges, spend countless hours solving complex problems, and achieve what others might not even attempt can become an addiction—an addiction to knowledge, to gaining experience, and to proving value through actions. It often feels like a game, where we are constantly earning experience points and developing our &amp;ldquo;character.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Everything Is Made from Something Previous: The Cycle of Copy, Transform, and Combine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/everythingisamixtape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:51:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/cheatsheet/thoughts/everythingisamixtape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Innovation does not emerge in a vacuum; it builds upon existing ideas and structures. The core of any screative process lies in three fundamental steps: &lt;strong&gt;copy&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;transform&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;combine&lt;/strong&gt;. These steps represent the foundation of human progress and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From language to technology, we inherently learn by mimicking what came before us. Copying is not theft—it’s the first stage of understanding and mastery. It’s only through absorbing and internalizing ideas that we can adapt and transform them into something new and innovative.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
